

KAMIL RĄPAŁA

IT SENIOR PROJECT MANAGER/Quality Leader

SUMMARY

Over 8 years I have been expanding my knowledge and acquiring skills in the ecommerce / IT industry. In my actual job, I am a project manager/scrum master and I put the satisfaction of my clients on the 1st place. I secure the continuity of online sales through effective technical support. I work with well-known online stores, supervise their development and security in the successive use of the Magento, PIM and Presta systems.

Gallup - 1. Achiever - 2. Individualization - 3. Strategic - 4. Communication - 5. Learner

DISC - Dominance - 40% / Influence - 35% / Conscientiousness - 15% / Steadiness - 10%

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- Project management
- Content Creation
- Public Relations
- Website Management
- Digital Analytic Tools
- Graphic Design
- Strong Communication Skills
- Team management
- Time management
- Project planning
- E-commerce

- QA manual test with creating a scenarios
- Magento 1&2, Pimcore, Hyva PrestaShop, Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, Gimp

Certificates (part)

- Google PMP
- Pimcore Consultant
- Newrelic Full Stack Observability Practitioner
- Generative AI Overview PMI
- PSM I

CONTACT DETAILS:

Telephone: 535 422 062

Email: rapala.kamil@gmail.com

City: Tarnów

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/kamilrąpała Portfolio: kamilr96.github.io/Portfolio/#home

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Gate-Software

SENIOR IT PROJECT MANAGER - (JULY 2020 - PRESENT)

- Establishing and maintaining customer relationships
- Analysis of customer requirements
- Creating and assigning tasks
- Coordinating task progress
- Controlling the budget Creating documentation
- Team management
- Cooperation with external companies
- Magento/Pimcore/Hyva consulting
- UX design/Creating mockups
- Preparing training
- Manual testing

 $\label{prop:eq:condition} \textit{Everything is preserved in Agile, Prince 2 and Scrum methodology}$

QUALITY LEADER - (JANUARY 2024 - PRESENT)

- Creating Workflows and Processes
- Process Optimization (Regularly review and improve workflows, integrating feedback and adapting to evolving project requirements while maintaining compliance with Agile and PRINCE2 standards)
- Creating Standards and Documentation
- Project Lifecycle Management Continuous Monitoring
- Documentation Creation and Management (Quality Guidelines and Protocols, Standard Operating Procedures, Knowledge Sharing)
- Onboarding Processes (Quality Onboarding Programs, Training and Development, Mentorship)
- Technical Recruitment for Second Stage Interviews (Skill Assessment, Cultural Fit Evaluation, Feedback and Decision-Making)
- Participation in Client Contracting (Client Alignment on Quality Standards, Quality Requirements and SLAs)

PMI PC Krakow Branch

EDUCATION LEADER - (JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT)

- Developing concepts, programs, writing scripts, conducting cultural classes, workshops and other forms of educational and cultural activities Participation and realisation in popular science shows at PMI meetings Seeking and implementing new forms of media and new cultural activities

- Development of scenarios for thematic educational paths
- Preparation of schedules, scenarios, descriptions and other documentation
- Creating offers and applications within the university
- Keeping statistics

Medpak

E-COMMERCE MANAGER, (AUGUST 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2020)

- Editing and adding new descriptions with photos to MedPak blog on the site, powered by PrestaShop
- Adding new products in the baselinker panel based on wordpress, to create html-based auctions at the sales channels Allegro, amazon, ebay, empik
- Using a customer service (SubiektGT) as a database to add new products from invoices and deliveries, checking prices, determine the margin for a given
- Analyzing the Allegro market for the health category through TradeWatch Creating complex lists in Excel
- Using slack, teams and trello in communications, presentation
- · Contact with goods suppliers and clients
- Searching for new products
- Spotting and fixing bugs
- Social media developments

dlaGentlemana

UX DESIGNER/ GRAPHIC DESIGNER - (AUGUST 2019 - APRIL 2020)

- Creating graphic designs for Facebook / Instagram
- promotional / advertising clips
- Taking care of the company's social profiles and other places of content marketing activities, such as blogs, newsletters, site and e-mailing campaigns

TonGraph

PROJECT MANAGER & UX DESIGNER (AUGUST 2017 - AUGUST 2018)

- Team management based on kanban boards.
- creating graphics for music bands, logos for creators from streaming channels, ads, banners or promoting specific brands for online stores.

 Moreover, preparation shorts intro / outro films and preparation of UX mockups for web applications and websites. Creating graphic designs for Facebook / Instagram
- promotional / advertising clips
- Using slack, teams and trello in communications, presentation.
- Contact with clients.

ACADEMIC HISTORY

Cracow University of Economics

Applied Computer Science (2019 - 2021) - Master degree

State Higher Vocational School in Tarnow

Applied Computer Science (2015 - 2019) - Bachelor in Engineering of Computer

. Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).